Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 01: County Reports, 1
  - Forest County
    - Fifty Years, 1919-1969; cuid962; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Franklin County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1935; cuid963; 1 Items (Box 43)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1976; cuid964; 1 Items (Box 44)
    - Agent Reports, 1977-1983; cuid966; 1 Items (Box 45)
    - Anniversary, 50th and 75th, 1917-1992; cuid967; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1978; cuid968; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Bicentennial, 1984; cuid969; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Correspondence, 2010-2011; cuid970 (Box 238)
  - Fulton County
    - Agent Reports, 1948-1965; cuid971; 1 Items (Box 45)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975; cuid972; 1 Items (Box 45)
  - Gettysburg, Adams County
    - Community Profile, undated; cuid973; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Greene County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1965; cuid974; 1 Items (Box 46)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1973; cuid975; 1 Items (Box 46)
    - Agent Reports, 1974-1975; cuid976; 1 Items (Box 47)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1980; cuid977; 1 Items (Box 47)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid978; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1996; cuid979; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2008 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 278)
  - Huntingdon County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1955; cuid980; 1 Items (Box 47)
    - Agent Reports, 1956-1976; cuid981; 1 Items (Box 48)
    - Annual Dinner Meeting, 72nd, 1989; cuid985; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Dinner Meeting, 73rd, 1990; cuid986; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 61st, 1978; cuid987; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 68th, 1985; cuid988; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid983; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - 4-H Awards Banquet, 1989; cuid984; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Indiana County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1940; cuid989; 1 Items (Box 48)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1976; cuid990; 1 Items (Box 49)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1980; cuid992; 1 Items (Box 50)
    - Anniversary, 75th, 1917-1992; cuid994; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1917-1967; cuid995; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid993; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Coleman, Lexi and Katie Wright Disciplinary Action, 2005 (Box 280)
  - Jefferson County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1960; cuid996; 1 Items (Box 50)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1965; cuid997; 1 Items (Box 51)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1983; cuid998; 1 Items (Box 51)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1916-1966; cuid999; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting and 4-H Leader Recognition, 1990/11/08; cuid1000; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1990; cuid1001; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1002; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Farms Guide, undated; cuid1003; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Juniata County
    - Agent Reports, 1918-1935; cuid1004; 1 Items (Box 51)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1980; cuid1005; 1 Items (Box 52)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1981; cuid1007; 1 Items (Box 53)
    - Annual Report, 1988; cuid1008; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Lackawanna County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1969; cuid1009; 1 Items (Box 53)
    - Agent Reports, 1970-1985; cuid1011; 1 Items (Box 54)
    - Annual Report, 1980; cuid1013; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1983; cuid1014; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1012; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Calendar of Events and Annual Report, 1996-1997; cuid1015; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Lancaster County
    - Agent Reports, 1913-1930; cuid1016; 1 Items (Box 54)
    - Agent Reports, 1931-1965; cuid1017; 1 Items (Box 55)
    - Agent Reports, 1966-1983; cuid1018; 1 Items (Box 56)
    - An Account of Four Journeys - George Washington in Lancaster, PA, 1932 (Box 263)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1913-1963; cuid1019; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986; cuid1020; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Narrative Reports, 1926-1952 (Box 263)
    - Annual Narrative Reports, 1954-1959 (Box 263)
    - Annual Narrative Reports, 1966 (Box 263)
    - Annual Narrative Reports, 1968 (Box 263)
    - Annual Reports, 1918-1924 (Box 263)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1990; cuid1021; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1994-2004 (Box 263)
    - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 277)
    - Application for Promotion to Senior Extension Agent - M. Maxwell Smith, 1955-1975 (Box 263)
    - Application for Promotion to Senior Extension Agent - M. Maxwell Smith, 1964-1981 (Box 263)
    - Committee Meeting Notes, 1924-1932 (Box 263)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2011; cuid1025 (Box 238)
    - Farm and Home Center, undated; cuid1022; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Meeting Notes, 1938-1956 (Box 263)
    - Meeting Notes (between farmers and local business men), 1913-1923 (Box 263)
    - 100 Years of Cooperative Extension, 2013 (Box 277)
    - Penn State Extension bulletins, 2005-2014 (Box 263)
    - Pennsylvania State Farm Show Winners, 1938-1980 (Box 263)
    - Potato Trials - Centre County, Lancaster County, undated; cuid1024; 1 Items (Box 178)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meetings, 2011; cuid1027 (Box 240)
    - SE Region CED Leadership Team Meetings, 2009-2010; cuid1026 (Box 240)
    - Summary of Cost of Production Records in Lancaster County, 1922-1960 (Box 263)
    - Tribute to Max, 1981 (Box 263)
    - Tribute to M. Max Smith, 1937-1981; cuid1023; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Lawrence County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1935; cuid1028; 1 Items (Box 56)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1980; cuid1029; 1 Items (Box 57)
    - Agent Reports, 1977-1980; cuid1031; 1 Items (Box 58)
    - Anniversary, 50th and 75th, 1919-1991; cuid1033; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1032; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 277)
  - Lebanon County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1960; cuid1034; 1 Items (Box 58)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1983; cuid1035; 1 Items (Box 59)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid1037; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Anniversary, 75th, 1917-1992; cuid1038; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1040; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1993; cuid1039; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2010; cuid1042 (Box 238)
    - Salute to Newton J. Bair, 1983; cuid1041; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meetings, 2010-2011; cuid1043 (Box 240)
  - Lehigh County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1940; cuid1045; 1 Items (Box 59)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1965; cuid1046; 1 Items (Box 60)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1982; cuid1047; 1 Items (Box 60)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1915-1965; cuid1049; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid1050; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1994; cuid1051; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2012 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report/Calendar of Events, 2000-2001 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report/Calendar of Events, 2005-2012 (Box 277)
    - Correspondence, 2007-2011; cuid1053 (Box 238)
    - Tribute to Partnership, 1980; cuid1052; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 (Box 250)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1976 (Box 250)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 251)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1997-2005 (Box 251)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 2006-2010 (Box 252)
    - Agriculture and Home Economics Monthly Reports, 1962-1966 (Box 252)
    - Agriculture Monthly Reports, 1964 (Box 252)
    - Agriculture Monthly Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 252)
    - Home Economics Monthly Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 252)
    - Monthly Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 252)
    - Home Economics Weekly Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 252)
    - Weekly Reports, 1953 (Box 252)
    - Weekly Reports, 1948 (Box 252)
    - Weekly Reports, 1943 (Box 252)
    - Weekly Reports, 1938 (Box 253)
    - Weekly Reports, 1933 (Box 253)
    - Monthly Reports, 1919-1926 (Box 253)
    - Weekly Reports, 1916-1918 (Box 253)
    - Annual Report, 1952-1965 (Box 253)
    - Annual Report, 1948-1951 (Box 254)
    - Agriculture Newsletters, 1971-1994 (Box 254)
    - Home Economics Newsletters, 1971-1989 (Box 254)
    - Leader Letters, 1970-1993 (Box 254)
    - 4-H Newsletters, 1979-1996 (Box 255)
    - Tasks and Narratives, 1971-1981 (Box 255)
    - County Monthly Time Distribution Worksheets, 1970-1977 (Box 255)
    - EMIS Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 255)
    - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 255)
    - Annual Meeting, 1936-1957 (Box 256)
    - County Plan of Work, 1972-1973 (Box 256)
    - EMIS Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 256)
    - Annual Reports, 1966-1987 (Box 256)
    - Tasks and Narratives, 1970-1971 (Box 256)
    - Narratives, 1969-1970 (Box 256)
    - County Meeting Report, 1969 (Box 256)
    - 4-H Newsletters, 1997-2005 (Box 256)
    - 4-H Leader Letters, 1994-2004 (Box 256)
    - Agriculture Newsletters, 1994-2007 (Box 257)
    - Home Economics Newsletters, 1990-2004 (Box 257)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1958-1961 (Box 257)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1957 (Box 258)
    - Allentown Fair clippings, 1958-1994 (Box 258)
    - Morning Call Clippings, 1963 (Box 258)
    - Farm Show clippings, 1961-1995 (Box 258)
    - Farm Show clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 258)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1995 (Box 259)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 260)
    - Growing Green clippings, 1982 (Box 260)
    - Growing Green clippings, 1995-2002 (Box 260)
    - Farm News, 1991-1999 (Box 260)
    - Farm News, 2000-2002 (Box 261)
    - Census of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 261)
    - Agricultural Statistics, 1999-2000 (Box 261)
    - Orchard and Vineyard Survey, 1972 (Box 261)
    - Extension Staff Planning Data, 1973 (Box 261)
    - Retail Farm Market Survey, 1968 (Box 261)
    - Census of Agriculture, 1954 (Box 261)
    - Poultry Statistics, 1909-1963 (Box 261)
    - Fruit and Grapevine Survey, 1967 (Box 261)
    - Christmas Tree Survey, 1962 (Box 261)
    - Dairy Statistics, 1962 (Box 261)
    - Irrigation Survey, 1968-1969 (Box 261)
    - Ranking Agricultural Counties, 1945 (Box 261)
    - Vegetable and Strawberry Statistics, 1918-1961 (Box 261)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1965-1974 (Box 261)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1959-1963 (Box 261)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1980-1983 (Box 261)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1976 (Box 261)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1984 (Box 262)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1985-1986 (Box 262)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1977-1979 (Box 262)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1975 (Box 262)
    - Orchard and Vineyard Survey, 1987 (Box 262)
    - Statistical Survey, 1988-1990 (Box 262)
    - Historic Livestock Statistics, 1960-1979 (Box 262)
    - Poultry Statistics, 1960-1984 (Box 262)
    - Regional Weather Summary, 1965 (Box 262)
    - Census of Agriculture, 1959 (Box 262)
    - Crops and Livestock Annual Summary, 1957-1958 (Box 262)
    - Potato Research Summary, 1966 (Box 262)
    - Horse and Pony Survey, 1966 (Box 262)
    - Fruit Tree and Grapevine Survey, 1964 (Box 262)
    - Statistics and Rankings by Counties, 1961 (Box 262)
    - Ranking of Pennsylvania Counties in Agriculture, 1964 (Box 262)
  - Luzerne County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1955; cuid1054; 1 Items (Box 61)
    - Agent Reports, 1956-1980; cuid1055; 1 Items (Box 62)
    - Agent Reports, 1985-1988; cuid1056; 1 Items (Box 62)
    - Agent Reports, 1981-1984; cuid1057; 1 Items (Box 63)
    - Anniversary, 25th, 1914-1919; cuid1060; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1914-1964; cuid1061; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1059; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1989; cuid1062; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1994; cuid1063; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 277)
    - Formulation of Farm Bureau, 1914; cuid1058; 1 Items (Box 125)
  - Lycoming County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1950; cuid1064; 1 Items (Box 63)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1980; cuid1065; 1 Items (Box 64)
    - Agent Reports, 1981-1985; cuid1066; 1 Items (Box 65)
    - Agent Reports, 1986-1988; cuid1067; 1 Items (Box 64)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1068; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1994-1996; cuid1069; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 277)
  - McKean County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1955; cuid1070; 1 Items (Box 65)
    - Agent Reports, 1956-1965; cuid1071; 1 Items (Box 66)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1983; cuid1072; 1 Items (Box 66)
    - Annual Report, 1988; cuid1073; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1916-1950; cuid1074; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 51st, 1967; cuid1075; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1969; cuid1076; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1983; cuid1077; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - McKean, Potter Counties
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid1078; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1995; cuid1079; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Mercer County
    - Agent Reports, 1912-1960; cuid1080; 1 Items (Box 67)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1965; cuid1081; 1 Items (Box 68)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1981; cuid1082; 1 Items (Box 68)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1083; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Anniversary, 75th, 1912-1987; cuid1084; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1912-1962; cuid1085; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 54th, 1966; cuid1086; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1980; cuid1087; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1983; cuid1088; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2009 (Box 277)
  - Mifflin County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1930; cuid1089; 1 Items (Box 68)
    - Agent Reports, 1931-1969; cuid1090; 1 Items (Box 69)
    - Agent Reports, 1970-1981; cuid1092; 1 Items (Box 70)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1093; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Mifflin, Juniata Counties
    - Annual Report, 1995; cuid1094; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Monroe County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1935; cuid1095; 1 Items (Box 70)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1975; cuid1096; 1 Items (Box 71)
    - Agent Reports, 1976-1988; cuid1097; 1 Items (Box 72)
    - Annual Program Highlights, 2007 (Box 277)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1098; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 278)
    - Summary Report, 1987; cuid1099; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Montgomery County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1950; cuid1100; 1 Items (Box 72)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1982; cuid1101; 1 Items (Box 73)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1912-1962; cuid1104; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1977; cuid1105; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 277)
    - CED Leadership Institute, 2009; cuid1118 (Box 240)
    - Correspondence, 2008-2011; cuid1117 (Box 238)
    - Dairy, 1940-1950; cuid1107; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Deppen, Marion R., 1950; cuid1108; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Farm Show, 1917-1950; cuid1109; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Farm Show, 1940-1950; cuid1110; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Farming Issues, 1950-1959; cuid1111; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - 4-H Program, 1940-1950; cuid1106; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Home Economics, 1940-1950; cuid1112; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Kiwanis, 1940-1950; cuid1113; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Meetings, Exhibits and Organizational Officers, 1940-1950; cuid1114; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting, 2011; cuid1119 (Box 240)
    - Senior Extension Club, 1940-1950; cuid1115; 1 Items (Box 172)
    - Waltz, Raymond Grover Sandy, 1940-1950; cuid1116; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Montour County
    - Agent Reports, 1937-1945; cuid1120; 1 Items (Box 73)
    - Agent Reports, 1946-1988; cuid1121; 1 Items (Box 74)
    - Agent Reports, 1968-1978; cuid1123; 1 Items (Box 104)
  - Montour, Northampton, Snyder, Union Counties
    - Annual Report, 1970; cuid1125; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1974; cuid1126; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1977; cuid1127; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1991; cuid1128; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1991-1992; cuid1129; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Northampton County
    - Agent Reports, 1920-1940; cuid1130; 1 Items (Box 74)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1980; cuid1131; 1 Items (Box 75)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1982; cuid1132; 1 Items (Box 76)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid1133; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1994; cuid1134; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report/Calendar of Events, 2000-2001 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2010; cuid1135 (Box 238)
  - Northumberland County
    - Agent Reports, 1918-1960; cuid1136; 1 Items (Box 76)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1967; cuid1137; 1 Items (Box 77)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1984; cuid1138; 1 Items (Box 77)
    - Agent Reports, 1968-1978; cuid1139; 1 Items (Box 104)
    - Agent Reports, 1987; cuid1140; 1 Items (Box 77)
    - Agent Reports, 1987; cuid1141; 1 Items (Box 77)
  - Northwest Region
    - Strategic Plans, 2004-2005 (Box 278)
  - Perry County
    - Agent Reports, 1921-1960; cuid1142; 1 Items (Box 77)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1983; cuid1143; 1 Items (Box 78)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1146; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1989; cuid1145; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Correspondence, 2010; cuid1147 (Box 238)
  - Philadelphia County
    - 20th Anniversary-Penn State Urban Gardening Program Banner, undated; cuid1148; 1 Items; Artifacts--Textiles--Banners (Box 201)
    - Accessible Garden/Herb and Flower Garden (Penn State Cooperative Extension Urban Gardening Program), circa 1990-1999; cuid1152; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 18" x 12"
    - Agent Reports, 1923-1950; cuid1153; 1 Items (Box 78)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1975; cuid1154; 1 Items (Box 79)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1982; cuid1155; 1 Items (Box 79)
    - American Community Gardening Association Conference, 1989, 1999; cuid1157; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Anniversary, 20th of Urban Gardening Program, 1977-1997; cuid1158; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 1998-2005; cuid1268 (Box 239)
    - Annual Report, 1990; cuid1159; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid1160; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1988-2003; cuid1161; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-2004; cuid1162; 1 Items (Box 198)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2003 (Box 280)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 50 Years, 2004 (Box 278)
    - Around Town publication, 1984-1990; cuid1163; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Autographed Apron, undated; cuid1164; 1 Items; Artifacts--Textiles--Clothing--Shirts (Box 201)
    - Awards and Recognition, 2000-2001; cuid1269 (Box 239)
    - Brochures, 2000-2004; cuid1270 (Box 239)
    - Christmas Card, cuid1165; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - City Council Budget Request, 1964; cuid1166; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - City Council Citation, 19841130; cuid1167; 1 Items (Box 198)
    - City Council Citation, 19930921; cuid1168; 1 Items (Box 198)
    - City Council Citation, 20040625; cuid1169; 1 Items (Box 198)
    - City Council, Legislators, 1999-2004; cuid1271 (Box 239)
    - City Gardener's Guide, cuid1170; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - City Green - Urban Gardening Program in Philadelphia, cuid1171; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - City of Philadelphia Proclamation, 19660428; cuid1172; 1 Items (Box 198)
    - Community Composting Education Program: Composting Demonstration, circa 1990-1999; cuid1173; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 18" x 24"
    - Community Garden (Urban Gardening Program), undated; cuid1174; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 24" x 18"
    - Community Garden Book, cuid1175; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Community Gardener's - Harvest Show, 1980-1983; cuid1176; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Community Gardening Procedural Manual, 1974; cuid1177; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Community Greening Review, 1994; cuid1178; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Community Greening Review, 2000, 2003; cuid1180; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Consumer Services Endowment, 1995; cuid1266 (Box 239)
    - Cook's Garden flyer, cuid1181; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2011; cuid1250 (Box 238)
    - Council Meetings, 1999-2001; cuid1267 (Box 239)
    - County Fair, 1992; cuid1182; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Creating Community Gardens, 1990; cuid1183; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Daily News Garden Guide, 1981; cuid1184; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Demonstration Garden Guide, cuid1185; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Don't Worry (Urban Gardening Program), March 27, 1966; cuid1186; 1 Items; Moving Image--Videotape--VHS
    - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1966; cuid1187; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Color (Box 199)
    - Extension, 1987-1988; cuid1188; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 199)
    - Extension Service - Harvest Show Superior Exhibit - certificate of excellence, 1993; cuid1189; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Fair, undated; cuid1190; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Fairmount Park Commission Advisory Council, 1996; cuid1191; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Family and Consumer Sciences, 2000-2003; cuid1264 (Box 239)
    - Farmers' Market Trust Fund Conference, 1999; cuid1256 (Box 239)
    - Focus on Youth and 4-H, 1960-1969; cuid1192; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows
    - Food and Agriculture - Policy Statement, cuid1193; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - 4-H Memory Garden-In Memory of Grace Hagerty, From Your Friends Wooden Sign, undated; cuid1150; 1 Items; Artifacts--Material Objects--Building Pieces (Box 201)
    - 4-H photo album, undated; cuid1151; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Albumen (Box 200)
    - 4-H Youth, 1999-2005; cuid1265 (Box 239)
    - Fruit Garden (Penn State Urban Gardening Program), circa 1990-1999; cuid1194; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 18" x 12"
    - Funding - Budget, 1999-2005; cuid1255 (Box 239)
    - Garden Tenders Basic Training Session 4, 2000/06/07; cuid1195; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Gardening Angels, 2000-2002; cuid1196; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Gardening in America, 1978; cuid1197; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Gardens for All - Gardener's Newsmagazine, 1984/09; cuid1198; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Getting Started Play (script for Gardening Fair), cuid1199; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Getting Started Play Script for Garden Fair, undated; cuid1200; 1 Items; Audio--Cassette--Standard
    - Grants and Proposals, 2000-2004; cuid1258 (Box 239)
    - Green Science Magazine, 1989; cuid1201; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Greene Towne Countrie Development Guide, 1988/06; cuid1202; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Harvest Show, cuid1203; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Horticulture, 1988-1990; cuid1204; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 199)
    - Horticulture Program, cuid1205; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Indoor Light Gardening Project for Philadelphia Schools, 1985; cuid1206; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Internal Staff Issues, 1999-2005; cuid1260 (Box 239)
    - IBM Programming, 2002-2004; cuid1263 (Box 239)
    - Jardin de la Comunidad (Urban Gardening Program), undated; cuid1207; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 24" x 18"
    - Magic Garden Model, cuid1208; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Marketing, 1999-2003; cuid1262 (Box 239)
    - Metropolitan Philadelphia and Its Future, 2001 (Box 278)
    - National Georgraphic Article - Gift of Gardening, 1992; cuid1209; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Office Procedures, 1999-2004; cuid1259 (Box 239)
    - Penn State Urban Gardening Program Banner, undated; cuid1210; 1 Items; Artifacts--Textiles--Banners (Box 201)
    - Penn State Urban Gardening Program Demostration Project, circa 1990-1999; cuid1211; 1 Items; Graphic--Posters, 12" x 18"
    - Penn State Urban Gardening Program T-Shirt, undated; cuid1212; 1 Items; Artifacts--Textiles--Clothing--Shirts (Box 199)
    - Philadelphia during Stevens/Kauffman tenure as Interim RDs, 2006; cuid1252 (Box 238)
    - Philadelphia Executive Board, 2000-2005; cuid1254 (Box 239)
    - Philadelphia Housing, 2004-2006; cuid1253 (Box 238)